0,1,2,3
Jim,NNP,B-NP,B-PER
Grabb,NNP,I-NP,I-PER
(,(,O,O
U.S.,NNP,B-NP,B-LOC
),),O,O
vs.,IN,B-PP,O
Sandon,NNP,B-NP,B-PER
Stolle,NNP,I-NP,I-PER
(,(,O,O
Australia,NNP,B-NP,B-LOC
),),O,O
