0,1,2,3
Poland,NNP,B-NP,B-LOC
-,:,O,O
Krzysztof,NNP,B-NP,B-PER
Warzycha,NNP,I-NP,I-PER
(,(,O,O
46th,JJ,B-NP,O
minute,NN,I-NP,O
),),O,O
",",",",O,O
Marcin,NNP,B-NP,B-PER
Mieciel,NNPS,I-NP,I-PER
