0,1,2,3
(,(,O,O
Norway,NNP,B-NP,B-LOC
),),O,O
",",",",O,O
Stephen,NNP,B-NP,B-PER
McAllister,NNP,I-NP,I-PER
",",",",O,O
Neal,NNP,B-NP,B-PER
Briggs,NNP,I-NP,I-PER
