0,1,2,3
6.,NNP,B-NP,O
Hans,NNP,I-NP,B-PER
de,NNP,I-NP,I-PER
Clerq,NNP,I-NP,I-PER
(,(,O,O
Belgium,NNP,B-NP,B-LOC
),),O,O
Palmans,NNS,B-NP,B-ORG
27,CD,B-NP,O
seconds,NNS,I-NP,O
