0,1,2,3
--,:,B-NP,O
Jason,NNP,I-NP,B-PER
Webb,NNP,I-NP,I-PER
",",",",O,O
Buenos,NNP,B-NP,B-ORG
Aires,NNP,I-NP,I-ORG
Newsroom,NNP,I-NP,I-ORG
+541,CD,I-NP,O
318-0655,JJ,I-NP,O
