0,1,2,3
At,IN,B-PP,O
Cardiff,NNP,B-NP,B-LOC
:,:,O,O
Kent,NNP,B-NP,B-ORG
255-3,CD,I-NP,O
(,(,O,O
D.,NNP,O,B-PER
Fulton,NNP,O,I-PER
64,CD,O,O
",",",",O,O
M.,NNP,B-NP,B-PER
Walker,NNP,I-NP,I-PER
59,CD,I-NP,O
",",",",O,O
C.,NNP,B-NP,B-PER
Hooper,NNP,I-NP,I-PER
