0,1,2,3
World,NNP,B-NP,B-ORG
Bridge,NNP,I-NP,I-ORG
30,CD,I-NP,O
03/09,CD,I-NP,O
South,NNP,I-NP,B-LOC
Korea,NNP,I-NP,I-LOC
/,SYM,O,O
Japan,NNP,B-NP,B-LOC
rnr,CC,I-NP,O
CNR,NNP,I-NP,B-ORG
.,.,O,O
