0,1,2,3
Todd,NNP,B-NP,B-PER
Woodbridge,NNP,I-NP,I-PER
(,(,O,O
Australia,NNP,B-NP,B-LOC
),),O,O
beat,VB,B-VP,O
Mark,NNP,B-NP,B-PER
Philippoussis,NNP,I-NP,I-PER
