0,1,2,3
6.,NNP,B-NP,O
Claus,NNP,I-NP,B-PER
Manne,NNP,I-NP,I-PER
Nielsen,NNP,I-NP,I-PER
(,(,O,O
Denmark,NNP,B-NP,B-LOC
),),O,O
KTM,NNP,B-NP,B-ORG
