0,1,2,3
At,IN,B-PP,O
Trent,NNP,B-NP,B-LOC
Bridge,NNP,I-NP,I-LOC
:,:,O,O
Nottinghamshire,NNP,B-NP,B-ORG
392-6,CD,I-NP,O
(,(,O,O
G.,NNP,B-NP,B-PER
Archer,NNP,I-NP,I-PER
143,CD,I-NP,O
not,RB,B-VP,O
