0,1,2,3
Alex,NNP,B-NP,B-PER
Corretja,NNP,I-NP,I-PER
(,(,O,O
Spain,NNP,B-NP,B-LOC
),),O,O
vs.,IN,B-PP,O
Byron,NNP,B-NP,B-PER
Black,NNP,I-NP,I-PER
(,(,O,O
Zimbabwe,NNP,B-NP,B-LOC
),),O,O
