0,1,2,3
David,NNP,B-NP,B-PER
Wheaton,NNP,I-NP,I-PER
(,(,O,O
U.S.,NNP,B-NP,B-LOC
),),O,O
vs.,IN,B-PP,O
Kevin,NNP,B-NP,B-PER
Kim,NNP,I-NP,I-PER
(,(,O,O
U.S.,NNP,B-NP,B-LOC
),),O,O
