0,1,2,3
Carlos,NNP,B-NP,B-PER
Costa,NNP,I-NP,I-PER
(,(,O,O
Spain,NNP,B-NP,B-LOC
),),O,O
vs.,IN,B-PP,O
Magnus,NNP,B-NP,B-PER
Gustafsson,NNP,I-NP,I-PER
(,(,O,O
Sweden,NNP,B-NP,B-LOC
),),O,O
