0,1,2,3
F.A.,NNP,B-NP,O
:,:,O,O
Ferris,NNPS,B-NP,B-ORG
",",",",O,I-ORG
Baker,NNP,B-NP,I-ORG
Watts,NNP,I-NP,I-ORG
",",",",O,I-ORG
Inc.,NNP,B-NP,I-ORG
",",",",O,O
Charleston,NNP,B-NP,B-LOC
