0,1,2,3
Finland,NN,B-NP,B-LOC
-,:,O,O
Ville,NNP,B-NP,B-PER
Peltonen,NNP,I-NP,I-PER
(,(,O,O
10th,JJ,B-NP,O
minute,NN,I-NP,O
),),O,O
",",",",O,O
Juha,NNP,B-NP,B-PER
Ylonen,NNP,I-NP,I-PER
(,(,O,O
10th,JJ,B-NP,O
),),O,O
",",",",O,O
