0,1,2,3
Martin,NNP,B-NP,B-PER
Gates,NNP,I-NP,I-PER
",",",",O,O
Anders,NNP,B-NP,B-PER
Haglund,NNP,I-NP,I-PER
(,(,O,O
Sweden,NNP,B-NP,B-LOC
),),O,O
