0,1,2,3
Cevaer,NNP,B-NP,B-PER
(,(,O,O
France,NNP,B-NP,B-LOC
),),O,O
",",",",O,O
Thomas,NNP,B-NP,B-PER
Bjorn,NNP,I-NP,I-PER
(,(,O,O
Denmark,NNP,B-NP,B-LOC
),),O,O
",",",",O,O
Tony,NNP,B-NP,B-PER
Johnstone,NNP,I-NP,I-PER
