0,1,2,3
3.,NNP,B-NP,O
Sven,NNP,I-NP,B-PER
Teutenberg,NNP,I-NP,I-PER
(,(,O,O
Germany,NNP,O,B-LOC
),),O,O
U.S.,NNP,B-NP,B-ORG
Postal,NNP,I-NP,I-ORG
