0,1,2,3
--,:,O,O
Huw,NNP,B-NP,B-PER
Jones,NNP,I-NP,I-PER
",",",",O,O
New,NNP,B-NP,B-ORG
York,NNP,I-NP,I-ORG
Commodities,NNP,I-NP,I-ORG
212-859-1646,CD,I-NP,O
