0,1,2,3
133,CD,B-NP,O
Ricky,NNP,I-NP,B-PER
Willison,NNP,I-NP,I-PER
69,CD,I-NP,O
64,CD,I-NP,O
",",",",O,O
Stephen,NNP,B-NP,B-PER
Ames,NNP,I-NP,I-PER
(,(,O,O
Trinidad,NNP,B-NP,B-LOC
and,CC,I-NP,I-LOC
Tobago,NNP,I-NP,I-LOC
),),O,O
