0,1,2,3
TBN,NNP,B-NP,B-ORG
30,CD,I-NP,O
6/9,CD,I-NP,O
Mideast,JJ,I-NP,B-LOC
/,SYM,O,O
W.C.,NNP,B-NP,B-LOC
India,NNP,I-NP,I-LOC
W200,CD,I-NP,O
",",",",O,O
E.C.India,NNP,B-NP,B-LOC
W195,NNP,I-NP,O
IOC,NNP,I-NP,B-ORG
.,.,O,O
