0,1,2,3
Northsea,NN,B-NP,B-ORG
Chaser,NN,I-NP,I-ORG
55,CD,I-NP,O
12/09,CD,I-NP,O
Mideast,JJ,I-NP,B-LOC
/,SYM,O,O
Japan,NNP,B-NP,B-LOC
W167.5,NNP,I-NP,O
Jomo,NNP,I-NP,B-ORG
.,.,O,O
