0,1,2,3
1.,CD,B-NP,O
Shayne,NNP,I-NP,B-PER
King,NNP,I-NP,I-PER
(,(,O,O
New,NNP,B-NP,B-LOC
Zealand,NNP,I-NP,I-LOC
),),O,O
KTM,NNP,B-NP,B-ORG
