0,1,2,3
5.,CD,B-NP,O
Collin,NNP,I-NP,B-PER
Dugmore,NNP,I-NP,I-PER
(,(,O,O
South,NNP,B-NP,B-LOC
Africa,NNP,I-NP,I-LOC
),),O,O
Honda,NNP,B-NP,B-ORG
