0,1,2,3
Gloria,NNP,B-NP,B-ORG
Bistrita,NNP,I-NP,I-ORG
-,:,O,O
Ilie,NNP,B-NP,B-PER
Lazar,NNP,I-NP,I-PER
(,(,O,O
32nd,CD,B-NP,O
),),O,O
",",",",O,O
Eugen,NNP,B-NP,B-PER
Voica,NNP,I-NP,I-PER
(,(,O,O
84th,CD,B-NP,O
),),O,O
